Dr. Ajay Pandey Mobile: 8527939298

E-Mail: drajay23pandey@gmail.com

#### **Career Summary-**

Qualified as **General management from IIM-Lucknow, MBA and BDS**, with more than 10 years of experience in clinical practice, marketing, operations and team handling. Looking for managerial role in healthcare, pharma, advertising, digital marketing and research sector. Worked and travelled all over India.

https://en.m.wikipedia.org/wiki/User:Excreator

Key skills-Marketing, Digital marketing-SEO, PPC/CPM, Data analysis, Web advertising, Online promotions, Blogs, medical content creation, Branding, Training, Advertising, ATL/BTL Activities, market research, pharmaceutical sciences, medical/dental sciences, product management, clinical research, healthcare and hospital knowledge, providing technical Training of Healthcare products and procedures to doctors and sales team, soft tissue LASER specialist, IT-Skill = MS-Word, Excel, Internet, MS-office, e-mail marketing, sms-marketing.

# **Blogs And Articles-**

O-RAY Dental Technologies: <a href="https://www.facebook.com/oraydentaltechnologies">https://www.facebook.com/oraydentaltechnologies</a>

Twitter: https://twitter.com/pandey 23ajay

LinkedIn: https://www.linkedin.com/mwlite/in/dr-ajay-pandey-445a211a

Naked scientists: http://www.thenakedscientists.com/forum/index.php?action=profile;area=showposts;u=27760

#### **Projects done-**

- 1. <u>Portal development- www.medexpoindia.com</u> the health analysis ecommerce portal (Pharma/Medical/cosmetic products) as Founder.
- 2. <u>Project on endodontic instrument and material</u>: assessing most commonly used brand and interest of doctors to use modern technology. Assessing reasons for not using advanced technology dental equipments. It was one month paid project. For *Dentsply-India pvt ltd*, *noida*.

### **Educational qualification-**

- 1. General Management (GMPE)-Indian institute of management-Lucknow. 2013 to 2014
  Grade-Good
- 2. MBA- Marketing, Project management. 2009 to 2011

Institute of co-operative and corporate management, Research and training, Lucknow, U.P, www.iccmrt.ac.in

Percentage- 66.34%, Division- First

3. BDS (Bachelor of Dental surgery)-2001 to 2006

Percentage- 67.16%, Division- First

Army college of Dental sciences, www.armycods.in, Telangana

4. Certifications:

Professional selling skill- certified by DENTSPLY-INDIA Pvt Ltd. www.dentsply-india.com

#### Work experience-

1. Wolters Kluwer India Pvt. Ltd: Since Feb 2016 to July 2017

**Designation:** Product Manager Marketing: Health

#### Job Profile-

- Marketing collateral & branding support for Health Print Books (More than 280 Indian Originals & 1500 US Titles).
- Digital Marketing support for health print books.
- Responsible for Pan India marketing communication to channel partners & internal team.
- Planning & supporting events in Medical/Dental Institutes.
- Innovating marketing communication as per market trend & Strategizing market communication via Email/What's app.
- Market & competitor research.
- Competition Product pricing and data analysis.

## 2. Skanray Technologies Pvt. Ltd: 2014 to 2015

Worked as product manager. *Job profile*- Scientific product demonstration, market research, CDE-Programme planning . KOL management. Visiting key clinics and hospitals. Branding and advertising the products. Customer complaint & query handling.

#### 3. Unicorn Denmart Pvt. Ltd. 2013 to 2014

Worked as RSM-South India for entire range of dental products, involving product demonstration for Dental LASER Units & x-rays.

### 4. Dentsply-India Pvt ltd: 2011 to 2012.

Worked as product specialist. *job profile*- Scientific product demonstration and marketing, CDE/CME-Programme planning. KOL management. Visiting key clinics and hospitals. Branding and advertising the products. Customer complaint & query handling.

## Personal profile-

Date of birth- 01 Jan 1981. Sex- Male. Father's name- Major R N Pandey. Marital status- married

Nationality- Indian.

**Language fluent with**- Hindi and English.

The said information is true to best of my knowledge and belief.